[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet of the Solar System has the most moons?", "correct_answer": "Jupiter", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Saturn", "Pluto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aardvark is a word coming from the Afrikaans/Dutch that literally translates as what?", "correct_answer": "Earth Pig", "incorrect_answers": ["Long Nose", "Ant Eater", "Pig Like"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What pathological phobia does Marnie have in Alfred Hitchcocks 1964 movie Marnie?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Color red", "Men", "Thunderstorms"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Wichita, the county seat of Sedgwick County, is nicknamed what?", "correct_answer": "Air Capital", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain Capital", "Plain Capital", "River capital"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many phases are there in a human cardiac cycle?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "1", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following planets is not named after a Roman god?", "correct_answer": "Uranus", "incorrect_answers": ["Neptune", "Jupiter", "Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film House of 1000 Corpses, what were Grandpa and Otis watching on the TV when the police arrived?", "correct_answer": "The Munsters", "incorrect_answers": ["Roswell", "Buffy the Vampire Slayer", "Miami Vice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Academy Award for Best Actress for her performance in the 1978 drama movie Coming Home?", "correct_answer": "Jane Fonda", "incorrect_answers": ["Maggie Smith", "Barbra Streisand", "Sophia Loren"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In December of 1979 the World Health Organization announced the eradication of what infectious disease?", "correct_answer": "Small Pox", "incorrect_answers": ["Measles", "Tuberculosis (TB)", "Malaria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What organization won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1999 for its medical care in acute crises and raising international awareness of potential humanitarian disasters?", "correct_answer": "Doctors Without Borders", "incorrect_answers": ["Amnesty International", "UNESCO", "International Red Cross"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of this legendary monster, which appears in Jewish folklore as an animated creature created from inanimate material?", "correct_answer": "Golem", "incorrect_answers": ["Grendel", "Draka", "Kraken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Charles Darwin major in at the University of Edinburgh where he joined his older brother in October 1825?", "correct_answer": "Medicine", "incorrect_answers": ["Geography", "Natural history", "Marine biology"]}]